{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Nguyen",
    "predicate": "property/shortDescription",
    "object": "Canadian filmmaker, activist and journalist",
    "human_readable": "Paul Nguyen's short description is Canadian filmmaker, activist and journalist.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6098013520240784,
            "question": "What is Paul Nguyen's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6093299984931946,
            "question": "What type of work does Paul Nguyen do as an activist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.528789758682251,
            "question": "How has Paul Nguyen used his journalism skills?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5182892084121704,
            "question": "Where is Paul Nguyen from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5098391175270081,
            "question": "What are some of the causes that Paul Nguyen supports as an activist?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5086110830307007,
            "question": "Name three roles that Paul Nguyen has held."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42111721634864807,
            "question": "Can you describe Paul Nguyen's work in a few words?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41970887780189514,
            "question": "Besides filmmaking, what other activities is Paul Nguyen involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40542522072792053,
            "question": "Is Paul Nguyen known for any specific film projects?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39549538493156433,
            "question": "What kind of films does Paul Nguyen make?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Nguyen's short description is Canadian filmmaker, activist and journalist.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1750_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Paul Nguyen known for any specific film projects?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1750_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides filmmaking, what other activities is Paul Nguyen involved in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1750_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe Paul Nguyen's work in a few words?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1750_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_137.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_170.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1750_57.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "The correct JSON response for the query \"Paul Nguyen's short description is Canadian filmmaker, activist and journalist.\" would be:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all the documents provided in the context information mention Paul Nguyen as a Canadian filmmaker, activist, and/or journalist."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the triple \"Paul Nguyen's short description is Canadian filmmaker, activist and journalist.\" Each of the provided text snippets describes Paul Nguyen as an activist, filmmaker, or journalist. Therefore, the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}